https://www.rwllaw.com/privacy-policy/

Hi, How Can We Help You?
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to your use of the Rifkin Weiner Livingston (RWL) website. Please review this policy carefully. Our web servers collect certain basic information about your computer and its connection to the Internet, such as the domain names and IP addresses of our visitors, automatically through the use of cookies. We may aggregate this information to measure various things about our website, such as the number of visitors and average time spent on the site. This statistical information is used to improve the content on our website, and is not associated with your personally identifiable information.
The only personally identifiable information we collect about you, such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address, is that which you choose to voluntarily submit to us by adding your name to our mailing or email lists or otherwise requesting information from RWL. We may use this information to contact you with general information about services that we believe might be of interest to you. While we will not sell your personally identifying information, we may provide your information to third parties. If you do not want your information shared with third parties, please do not provide personally identifiable information to us.
If you are a current subscriber to our mailing and/or email list and wish to update your information or be removed at any time, please contact Stacy Renauld by emailing srenauld@rwllaw.com, calling 410.269.5066, faxing 410.269.1235, or writing Stacy Renauld, Rifkin Weiner Livingston LLC, 225 Duke of Gloucester Street, Annapolis, Maryland 21401.
RWL may amend its privacy policy at any time without advance notice; however, all new privacy policies will be promptly posted on our website.
PLEASE BE AWARE THAT EACH CASE IS DIFFERENT AND THE PAST RECORD IS NO ASSURANCE OF FAVORABLE RESULTS IN ANY FUTURE CASE.
©2020 Rifkin Weiner Livingston LLC - Maryland's Local Law Firm®
State Capital Area
225 Duke of Gloucester Street
Annapolis, Maryland 21401
410.269.5066 (tel)
410.269.1235 (fax)
Baltimore City
2002 Clipper Park Road, Suite 108
Baltimore, Maryland 21211
410.769.8080 (tel)
410.769.8811 (fax)
Washington, D.C. Metropolitan Area
4800 Hampden Lane, Suite 820
Bethesda, Maryland 20814
301.951.0150 (tel)
301.951.0172 (fax)
Connect with RWL
